<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!-- Copyright 2016 Matthias Clasen -->
<component type="desktop">
  <id>com.gexperts.Tilix.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>MPL-2.0</project_license>
  <name>Tilix</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh_CN">Tilix</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">Tilix</name>
  <name xml:lang="tr">Tilix</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">Tilix</name>
  <name xml:lang="sr">Тајликс</name>
  <name xml:lang="ru">Tilix</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt_PT">Tilix</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt_BR">Tilix</name>
  <name xml:lang="pl">Tilix</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">Tilix</name>
  <name xml:lang="nb_NO">Tilix</name>
  <name xml:lang="ko">Tilix</name>
  <name xml:lang="ja">Tilix</name>
  <name xml:lang="it">Tilix</name>
  <name xml:lang="id">Tilix</name>
  <name xml:lang="he">Tilix</name>
  <name xml:lang="fr">Tilix</name>
  <name xml:lang="fi">Tilix</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">Tilix</name>
  <name xml:lang="en">Tilix</name>
  <name xml:lang="de">Tilix</name>
  <name xml:lang="cs">Tilix</name>
  <name xml:lang="bg">Tilix</name>
  <summary>A tiling terminal for GNOME</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh_CN">GNOME 的平铺终端模拟器</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Мозаїчний термінал для Gnome</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="tr">GNOME için döşeyen bir terminal</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">En sida-vid-sida-terminal för GNOME</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sr">Плочасти терминал за Гном</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ru">Тайлинговый терминал для GNOME</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt_PT">Um terminal em mosaico para o GNOME</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt_BR">Um terminal em mosaico para o GNOME</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pl">Emuluje działanie terminala w środowisku GNOME wykorzystując interfejs kafli</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Een terminal voor GNOME met tegelmogelijkheid</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ko">그놈을 위한 타일링 터미널</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="it">Un terminale a riquadri per GNOME</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="he">מסוף בריצוף עבור GNOME</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fr">Un terminal scindable pour GNOME</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fi">Laatoittava pääte Gnomelle</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Una terminal divisible para GNOME</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="en">A tiling terminal for GNOME</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="de">Ein Terminal für GNOME mit Kacheldarstellung</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="cs">Dlaždicový terminál pro GNOME</summary>
  <description>
    <p>
      Tilix is a tiling terminal emulator.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="zh_CN">Tilix 是一个平铺终端模拟器。</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Tilix - мозаїчний емулятор термінала.</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">Tilix döşeyen bir terminal emülatörüdür.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Tilix är en terminalemulator där terminaler placeras sida vid sida.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr">Тајликс је плочасти опонашавач терминала.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ru">Tilix является тайлинговым эмулятором терминала.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt_BR">Tilix é um emulador de terminal em mosaico.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Tilix jest emulatorem terminala obsługującym kafle.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Tilix is een terminalapplicatie met tegelmogelijkheid.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">Tilix 는 타일링 터미널 에뮬레이터 입니다.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Tilix è un emulatore di terminale a riquadri.</p>
    <p xml:lang="he">Tilix הוא מדמה מסוף עם ריצוף.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Tilix est un émulateur de terminal scindable.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">Tilix on laatoittava pääte-emulaattori.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Tilix es un emulador de terminal divisible.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en">Tilix is a tiling terminal emulator.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Tilix ist ein Terminal-Emulator mit Kacheldarstellung.</p>
    <p xml:lang="cs">Tilix je dlaždicový emulátor terminálu.</p>
    <p>It lets you:</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh_CN">它可让你：</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Він дозволяє:</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">Sağlar:</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Den låter dig:</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr">Омогућава вам да:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ru">Это позволяет:</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt_PT">Ele permite:</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt_BR">Ele permite:</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Pozwala użytkownikowi na:</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Het stelt u in staat om:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">다음과 같은 것을 할 수 있게 해 줍니다:</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Ti consente di:</p>
    <p xml:lang="id">Ini memungkinkan Anda:</p>
    <p xml:lang="he">ביכולתו:</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Il vous permet :</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">Sen avulla voit:</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Le permite:</p>
    <p xml:lang="en">It lets you:</p>
    <p xml:lang="el">Σας επιτρέπει να:</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Damit können Sie:</p>
    <p xml:lang="cs">Je v něm možné:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Layout terminals in any fashion by splitting them horizontally or vertically</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh_CN">通过垂直和水平分割随心所欲地排布终端</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Компонувати термінали в будь-якому вигляді, розділивши їх горизонтально та вертикально</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">Terminalleri, onları düşey veya dikey ayıracak şekilde düzenle</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Ändra layout för terminaler på vilket sätt som helst genom att dela dem horisontellt eller vertikalt</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr">Распоредите терминале како год пожелите тако што ћете их раздвојити водоравно или усправно</li>
      <li xml:lang="ru">Компоновать терминалы можно любым способом, путем разделения их по горизонтали или по вертикали</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt_PT">Dispor terminais de diferentes maneiras, dividindo-os horizontalmente ou verticalmente</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt_BR">Dispor terminais de diferentes maneiras, dividindo-os horizontalmente ou verticalmente</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">rozmieszczanie terminali w dowolny sposób, dzieląc je pionowo lub poziomo,</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Terminals indelen op welke manier dan ook door ze horizontaal of verticaal te splitsen</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">터미널을 가로 또는 세로로 분할하여 원하는 방식으로 배치하세요</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">disporre di più terminali multipli su un'unica finestra dividendola orizzontalmente o verticalmente</li>
      <li xml:lang="he">פריסת מסופים בכל דרך באמצעות פיצולם, אופקית או אנכית</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">D'organiser les terminaux de toutes les façons en les divisant horizontalement et verticalement</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">Määrittää päätteiden asettelun millä tavoin tahansa jakamalla pääteikkunan vaaka- tai pystysuunnassa</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Distribuir las terminales dividiéndolas horizontalmente o verticalmente</li>
      <li xml:lang="en">Layout terminals in any fashion by splitting them horizontally or vertically</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Terminals durch horizontales oder vertikales Teilen beliebig anordnen</li>
      <li xml:lang="cs">Rozmístit terminály libovolným rozdělením vodorovně či svisle</li>
      <li>Terminals can be re-arranged using drag and drop both within and between windows</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh_CN">可通过在窗口内外拖放重新安排终端</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Термінали можна впорядковувати перетягуванням у вікнах і між ними</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">Terminaller sürükle ve bırak kullanarak pencereler içinde ve arasında yeniden düzenlenebilir</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Terminaler kan omplaceras genom att dra och släppa dem både inom och mellan fönster</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr">Терминали се могу прерасподелити повлачењем и пуштањем унутар или између прозора</li>
      <li xml:lang="ru">Терминалы могут быть перестроены с помощью перетаскивания как внутри, так и между окнами</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt_PT">Reorganizar terminais arrastando e soltando em uma mesma janela, ou entre janelas diferentes</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt_BR">Reorganizar terminais arrastando e soltando em uma mesma janela, ou entre janelas diferentes</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">przenoszenie terminali pomiędzy oknami przeciągając je,</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Terminals kunnen anders worden ingedeeld middels slepen-en-neerzetten binnen en tussen vensters</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">창 안이나 창 사이에서 끌어옮겨 터미널을 재배열 할 수 있습니다</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">riordinare i terminali mediante trascinamento</li>
      <li xml:lang="he">ארגון מחדש של מסופים באמצעות גרירה ושחרור מחוץ לחלונות ובתוכם</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Les terminaux peuvent être réorganisés en utilisant le glisser-déposer dans une même fenêtre ou entre les fenêtres</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">Järjestää päätteitä vetämällä ja pudottamalla saman tai eri ikkunoiden välillä</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Las terminales pueden ser reordenadas arrastrando y soltando entre ventanas</li>
      <li xml:lang="en">Terminals can be re-arranged using drag and drop both within and between windows</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Terminals durch ziehen und ablegen sowohl innerhalb eines Fensters als auch zwischen Fenstern neu anordnen</li>
      <li xml:lang="cs">Přesouvat terminály přetažením uvnitř oken i mezi okny</li>
      <li>Terminals can be detached into a new window via drag and drop</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh_CN">可通过拖放将终端脱离为新的窗口</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Термінали можна від'єднати в нове вікно через перетягування</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">Terminaller sürükle ve bırak ile yeni bir pencereye ayrılabilir</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Terminaler kan kopplas loss till ett nytt fönster genom att dra och släppa dem</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr">Терминали се могу откачити у нове прозоре повлачењем и пуштањем</li>
      <li xml:lang="ru">Терминалы могут быть отделены в новое окно с помощью перетаскивания</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt_PT">Separar terminais em novas janelas arrastando e soltando</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt_BR">Separar terminais em novas janelas arrastando e soltando</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">odłączanie terminali do nowych okien przeciągając je,</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Terminal kunnen worden veranderd in een nieuw venster middels slepen-en-neerzetten</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">터미널을 끌어옮겨 새 창으로 분리 할 수 있습니다</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">spostare i terminali da una finestra all'altra mediante trascinamento</li>
      <li xml:lang="he">ניתוק מסופים לחלון חדש באמצעות גרירה ושחרור</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Les terminaux peuvent être détachés en une nouvelle fenêtre via un glisser-déposer</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">Asettaa päätteen uuteen ikkunaan vetämällä ja pudottamalla</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Las terminales se pueden mover a una ventana nueva vía arrastrar y soltar</li>
      <li xml:lang="en">Terminals can be detached into a new window via drag and drop</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Terminals per ziehen und ablegen als neues Fenster loslösen</li>
      <li xml:lang="cs">Přetažením odpojit terminály do nového okna</li>
      <li>Input can be synchronized between terminals so commands typed in one terminal are replicated to the others</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh_CN">可在终端之间同步输入，可将一个终端的输入复制到另一个终端里</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Введення можна синхронізувати між терміналами, тож команди, які будуть вводитись, будуть повторюватись на інших терміналах</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">Giriş terminaller arasında eşitlenebilir böylece bir terminalde yazılan komutları diğerlerine kopyalanır</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Inmatning kan synkroniseras mellan terminaler så att kommandon som skrivs in i en terminal upprepas till de andra</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr">Улаз се може ускладити између терминала тако да се нареде унете у једном терминалу одразе на друге</li>
      <li xml:lang="ru">Ввод может быть синхронизирован между терминалами, поэтому команды набранные в одном терминале, повторяются на другие</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt_PT">Sincronizar a entrada entre diferentes terminais, replicando comandos digitados em um terminal para outros</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt_BR">Sincronizar a entrada entre diferentes terminais, replicando comandos digitados em um terminal para outros</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">synchronizowanie wejścia pomiędzy terminalami, co umożliwia powielanie poleceń wprowadzonych w jednym terminalu,</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">De invoer kan worden gesynchroniseerd tussen terminals zodat opdrachten uit de ene terminal kunnen worden hergebruikt in andere terminals</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">터미널 사이 입력을 동기화 할 수 있으며 한 터미널에서의 입력이 다른 터미널에 복제 됩니다</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">sincronizzare l'input tra più terminali, così che i comandi digitati in un terminale sono replicati negli altri</li>
      <li xml:lang="he">סנכרון קלט בין מסופים כך שפקודה המוזנת לאחד מועתקת לאחרים</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">L'entrée peut être synchronisée entre les terminaux de façon à ce que les commandes saisies dans un terminal soient répliquées vers les autres</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">Syöte on mahdollista synkronoida eri päätteiden välillä, joten yhteen päätteeseen kirjoitetut komennot voidaan replikoida muihin päätteisiin</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">La entrada puede ser sincronizada entre terminales haciendo que los comandos introducidos en una se repliquen en las otras</li>
      <li xml:lang="en">Input can be synchronized between terminals so commands typed in one terminal are replicated to the others</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Die Eingabe zwischen Terminals synchronisieren, um Befehle in einem Terminal auf ein anderes zu replizieren</li>
      <li xml:lang="cs">Synchronizovat vstup mezi terminály, aby se příkazy zadávané v jednom replikovaly v dalších</li>
      <li>The grouping of terminals can be saved and loaded from disk</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh_CN">可从磁盘保存和载入终端分组</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Групування терміналів можна зберегти і завантажити з диска</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">Terminallerin gruplaması kaydedilebilir ve diskten yüklenebilir</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Grupperingen av terminaler kan sparas och läsas in från disk</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr">Начин распоређивања терминала се може сачувати и учитати са диска</li>
      <li xml:lang="ru">Группировка терминалов может быть сохранена и загружена с диска</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt_PT">Carregar e salvar grupos de terminais de/para o disco</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt_BR">Carregar e salvar grupos de terminais de/para o disco</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">grupowanie terminali, zapisywanie grup na dysku i wczytywanie ich,</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Gegroepeerde terminals kunnen worden opgeslagen naar en geladen vanaf een schijf</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">터미널 그루핑은 디스크에 저장하거나 불러올 수 있습니다</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">salvare e caricare successivamente da disco il raggruppamento dei terminali</li>
      <li xml:lang="he">שמירה וטעינה של קיבוץ המסופים</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Les groupes de terminaux peuvent être enregistrés et chargés depuis le disque</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">Päätteiden ryhmittely on mahdollista tallentaa ja ladata levyltä</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">La agrupación de terminales se puede guardar y cargar desde el disco</li>
      <li xml:lang="en">The grouping of terminals can be saved and loaded from disk</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Die Gruppierung der Terminals speichern und vom Datenträger laden</li>
      <li xml:lang="cs">Ukládat seskupení terminálů a pak je později opět načítat z úložiště</li>
      <li>Terminals support custom titles</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh_CN">终端支持自定义标题</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Термінали підтримують власні заголовки</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">Terminaller özel başlıkları destekler</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Terminaler stöder anpassade titlar</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr">Терминали подржавају прилагођене наслове</li>
      <li xml:lang="ru">Терминалы поддерживают пользовательские названия</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt_PT">Atribuir títulos personalizados aos terminais</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt_BR">Atribuir títulos personalizados aos terminais</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">nadawanie własnych tytułów terminali,</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">De terminals hebben ondersteuning voor aangepaste titels</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">터미널은 사용자 정의 제목을 지원합니다</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">personalizzare i titoli dei terminali</li>
      <li xml:lang="he">תמיכה בהתאמה אישית של כותרות המסופים</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Les terminaux acceptent les titres personnalisés</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">Päätteet tukevat omavalintaisia otsikoita</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Las terminales soportan títulos personalizados</li>
      <li xml:lang="en">Terminals support custom titles</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Terminals unterstützen benutzerdefinierte Titel</li>
      <li xml:lang="cs">Nastavit terminálům vlastní titulky</li>
      <li>Color schemes are stored in files and custom color schemes can be created by simply creating a new file</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh_CN">配色方案存储在文件中，可通过创建文件来创建新的配色方案</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Схеми кольорів збережено у файлах і власні схеми кольорів додаються через звичайне створення нових файлів</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">Renk düzenleri dosyalarda depolanır ve özel renk düzenleri sadece yeni bir dosya oluşturarak yaratılabilir</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Färgscheman lagras i filer och anpassade färgscheman kan enkelt skapas genom att skapa en ny fil</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr">Шеме боје се чувају у датотекама и прилагођене шеме боје се могу једноставно направити са новом датотеком</li>
      <li xml:lang="ru">Цветовые схемы сохраняются в файлах и пользовательские цветовые схемы могут быть созданы путем простого создания нового файла</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt_PT">Criar e armazenar novos esquemas de cores personalizados apenas manipulando arquivos</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt_BR">Criar e armazenar novos esquemas de cores personalizados apenas manipulando arquivos</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">przechowywanie zestawów kolorów w plikach i tworzenie własnych zestawów kolorów,</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Kleurenschema's worden opgeslagen in bestanden en aangepaste kleurenschema's kunnen worden gecreëerd door het creëren van een nieuw bestand</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">색상 스키마는 파일에 보관되며 사용자 정의 색상 스키마는 단순히 새 파일 생성으로 생성 될 수 있습니다</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">memorizzare gli schemi dei colori su file e crearne nuovi personalizzati semplicemente creando nuovi file</li>
      <li xml:lang="he">אחסון תכניות צבעים בקבצים ויצירת תכניות צבעים חדשות באמצעות יצירת קובץ חדש</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Les palettes de couleurs sont enregistrées dans des fichiers et des palettes de couleurs personnalisées peuvent être créées simplement en créant un nouveau fichier</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">las combinaciones de colores se guardan en archivos y es posible crear combinaciones personalizadas tan solo con un archivo nuevo</li>
      <li xml:lang="en">Color schemes are stored in files and custom color schemes can be created by simply creating a new file</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Farbschemata werden in Dateien gespeichert und benutzerdefinierte Farbschemata können durch Anlegen einer Datei erstellt werden</li>
      <li xml:lang="cs">Barevná schémata jsou uložena v souborech a vlastní můžete vytvořit prostým vytvořením nového souboru</li>
      <li>Transparent background</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh_CN">透明背景</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Прозоре тло</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">Şeffaf arkaplan</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Transparent bakgrund</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr">Провидна позадина</li>
      <li xml:lang="ru">Прозрачный фон</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt_PT">Utilizar plano de fundo transparente</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt_BR">Utilizar plano de fundo transparente</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">ustalenie przezroczystego tła,</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Doorzichtige achtergrond</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">투명한 배경</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Sfondo trasparente</li>
      <li xml:lang="id">Latar belakang transparan</li>
      <li xml:lang="he">רקע שקוף</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Arrière-plan transparent</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">Läpinäkyvä tausta</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Fondo transparente</li>
      <li xml:lang="en">Transparent background</li>
      <li xml:lang="el">Διαφανές παρασκήνιο</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Transparenter Hintergrund</li>
      <li xml:lang="cs">Průhledné pozadí</li>
      <li xml:lang="bg">Прозрачен фон</li>
      <li>Supports notifications when processes are completed out of view</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh_CN">支持进程在视图外完成时发送桌面通知</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Підтримування сповіщень, коли дії завершується позаочно</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">İşlemler görünüm dışında tamamlandığında bildirimleri destekler</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Stöder aviseringar då processer utom synhåll blir klara</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr">Подржава обавештења када се ненадгледани процеси заврше</li>
      <li xml:lang="ru">Поддержка уведомлений, когда процессы завершаются вне поля зрения</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt_PT">Receber notificações quando processos terminarem em segundo plano</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt_BR">Receber notificações quando processos terminarem em segundo plano</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Powiadamianie o zakończonych procesach, które są niewidoczne.</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Ondersteunt meldingen voor processen die buiten het zicht worden voltooid</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">뷰 밖에서 프로세스를 끝날때에 대한 알림 지원</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Notifica il completamento dei processi quando il terminale non è visibile</li>
      <li xml:lang="he">תמיכה בהתראות בסיום תהליכים מחוץ לתצוגה</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Prend en charge les notifications de bureau quand les processus s'achèvent en arrière-plan</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">Tukee ilmoituksia, kun prosessit valmistuvat ilman että ne ovat näkyvissä</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Soporte de notificaciones para procesos finalizados fuera de la vista</li>
      <li xml:lang="en">Supports notifications when processes are completed out of view</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Unterstützt Benachrichtigungen, wenn nicht sichtbare Prozesse beendet werden</li>
      <li xml:lang="cs">Podporuje oznamování o skončení procesů v nezaměřeném okně</li>
    </ul>
    <p>
      The application was written using GTK 3 and an effort was made to conform to
      GNOME Human Interface Guidelines (HIG). As a result, it does use client-side-decorations, though it can be disabled if necessary.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="zh_CN">该应用程序使用 GTK 3 编写并尝试兼容 GNOME 人机交互指南（HIG）。因此，Terminix 使用了客户端窗口装饰（CSD），但此功能可随时关闭。</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Програма написана з використанням GTK 3 і дотримується настанов щодо правил побудови інтерфейсу (GNOME HIG). У результаті, використовується оздоблення на боку клієнта, хоча його можна вимкнути, якщо потрібно.</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">Uygulama GTK 3 kullanarak yazılmıştır ve GNOME İnsan Arabirim Yönergelerine (HIG) uyması için çaba harcanmıştır. Sonuç olarak, istemci tarafı süslemeleri kullanır, yine de gerekirse bunlar devre dışı bırakılabilir.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Programmet skrevs med GTK 3 och försöker följa GNOME:s riktlinjer för mänskliga gränssnitt (HIG). Som ett resultat av detta använder det dekorationer från klientsidan, men det kan inaktiveras om nödvändigt.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr">Програм је написан уз помоћ ГТК 3 технологије и начињем је напор да буде у складу са Гномовим смерницама за развој програма (HIG). Због тога се користе декорације на клијентској страни али се он емогу онемогућити ако је то потребно.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ru">Приложение было написано с использованием GTK 3 и были предприняты усилия, чтобы они соответствовали GNOME Human Interface Guidelines (HIG). В результате, оно используется на стороне клиента-украшения, хотя оно может быть отключено, если это необходимо.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt_PT">A aplicação utiliza o GTK 3, observando as diretrizes de interface de usuário do GNOME (GNOME HIG). Portanto, decorações de janela internas são utilizadas, mas podem ser desabilitadas se necessário.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt_BR">A aplicação utiliza o GTK 3, observando as diretrizes de interface de usuário do GNOME (GNOME HIG). Portanto, decorações de janela internas são utilizadas, mas podem ser desabilitadas se necessário.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Program opracowano używając GTK3, zachowując wytyczne GNOME Human Interface Guidelines (HIG). W wyniku tego wyświetla on obramowania po stronie klienta, choć w razie potrzeby można je wyłączyć.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">De applicatie is geschreven in GTK 3 en er is veel moeite gestoken in het volgen van de richtlijnen van de HIG (GNOME Human Interface Guidelines). Dit resulteert in het gebruik van client-side-decorations maar deze kunnen, indien nodig, worden uitgeschakeld.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">이 앱은 GTK3 로 작성 되었으며 그놈 휴먼 인터페이스 가이드라인(HIG) 에 따르고자 노력 했습니다. 결과적으로, 이 앱은 클라이언트 측 데코레이션을 사용하며, 필요한 경우 비활성화 될 수 있습니다.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">L'applicazione è scritta in GTK 3 e si conforma alle GNOME Human Interface Guidelines (HIG). Di conseguenza fa uso di client-side-decorations, anche se possono essere disattivate, se necessario.</p>
    <p xml:lang="he">היישום נכתב באמצעות GTK 3 ונעשה מאמץ להתאימו להנחיות לממשק אנוש (HIG) של GNOME. כתוצאה מכך, נעשה שימוש בקישוטי צד־לקוח, אם כי ניתן להשביתם בעת הצורך.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">L'application a été écrite en utilisant GTK 3 et un effort a été fait pour se conformer aux GNOME Human Interface Guidelines (HIG). En conséquence, elle utilise des décorations côté client, bien qu'elles puissent être désactivées si nécessaire.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">La aplicación fue escrita usando GTK 3 realizando un esfuerzo en cumplir las Directrices de Interfaz Humana de GNOME (HIG). Como resultado, se utilizan decoraciones en el lado del cliente, aunque se pueden desactivar si fuera necesario.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en">The application was written using GTK 3 and an effort was made to conform to GNOME Human Interface Guidelines (HIG). As a result, it does use client-side-decorations, though it can be disabled if necessary.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Die Anwendung wurde mit GTK 3 geschrieben und es wurde Wert darauf gelegt, den GNOME Human Interface Guidelines (HIG) zu entsprechen. Infolgedessen werden Client Side Decorations verwendet, die aber bei Bedarf deaktiviert werden können.</p>
    <p xml:lang="cs">Tato aplikace je napsána pomocí GTK 3 a snahou bylo zůstat v souladu se Zásadami lidského rozhraní (HIG) GNOME. Ve výsledku tedy Tilix využívá dekorace na straně klienta, umí je však v případě nutnosti i vypnout.</p>
    <p>Tilix has been tested with GNOME and with Unity.</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh_CN">Tilix 已在 GNOME 和 Unity 上测试。</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Tilix випробувано з GNOME і Unity.</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">Tilix, GNOME'la ve Unity ile test edilmiştir.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Tilix har testats med GNOME och med Unity.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr">Тајликс је испробан на Гному и Јунитију.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ru">Tilix был протестирован с GNOME и Unity.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt_BR">O Tilix foi testado nos ambientes GNOME e Unity.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Tilix przetestowano z GNOME i Unity.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Tilix is getest onder GNOME en Unity.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">Tilix 는 그놈과 유니티에서 시험되었습니다.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Tilix è stato testato su GNOME e Unity.</p>
    <p xml:lang="he">Tilix נבדק עם GNOME ועם Unity.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Tilix a été testé sous GNOME et sous Unity.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">Tilix on testattu Gnomessa ja Unityssa.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Tilix ha sido probado en GNOME y en Unity.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en">Tilix has been tested with GNOME and with Unity.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Tilix wurde mit GNOME und Unity getestet.</p>
    <p xml:lang="cs">Tilix je testován v GNOME a Unity.</p>
  </description>
  <screenshots>
​   <screenshot type="default">https://gnunn1.github.io/tilix-web/assets/images/gallery/tilix-screenshot-1.png</screenshot>
    <screenshot>https://gnunn1.github.io/tilix-web/assets/images/gallery/tilix-screenshot-2.png</screenshot>
    <screenshot>https://gnunn1.github.io/tilix-web/assets/images/gallery/tilix-screenshot-3.png</screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <kudos>
    <kudo>AppMenu</kudo>
    <kudo>HiDpiIcon</kudo>
    <kudo>ModernToolkit</kudo>
    <kudo>Notifications</kudo>
  </kudos>
  <url type="homepage">https://gnunn1.github.io/tilix-web/</url>
  <url type="help">https://gnunn1.github.io/tilix-web/manual/</url>
  <url type="faq">https://gnunn1.github.io/tilix-web/faq</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://github.com/gnunn1/tilix/issues</url>
  <url type="translate">https://hosted.weblate.org/projects/tilix/translations/</url>
  <translation type="gettext">tilix</translation>
  <provides>
    <binary>tilix</binary>
  </provides>
</component>
